[
    {
      "question": "What does RM& IPR stand for?",
      "choices": [
        "researcher",
        "research",
        "researchers",
        "a good research objective"
      ],
      "type": "mcq",
      "answer_index": 1,
      "answer_text": "research",
      "explanation": "It is obvious that the number of papers relevant to a particular researcher is very few",
      "context_snippet": "RM& IPR– BRMK557. Syllabus Literature Review and Technical Reading, New and Existing Knowledge, Analysis and Synthesis of Prior Art, Bibliographic Databases: Web of Science, Google and Google Scholar, Effective Search: The Way Forward. A good literature survey is typically a two-step process as enumerated below. Identify the major topics or subtopics or concepts relevant to the subject under consideration. Place the citation of the relevant source (article/patent/website/data, etc.) in the corre"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are instruction manuals called?",
      "choices": [
        "datasheets",
        "BIT Page 6 RM& IPR– BRMK557",
        "documents",
        "resources"
      ],
      "answer_index": 0,
      "answer_text": "datasheets",
      "explanation": "Datasheets are instruction manuals",
      "context_snippet": "RM& IPR– BRMK557. Syllabus Literature Review and Technical Reading, New and Existing Knowledge, Analysis and Synthesis of Prior Art, Bibliographic Databases: Web of Science, Google and Google Scholar, Effective Search: The Way Forward. A good literature survey is typically a two-step process as enumerated below. Identify the major topics or subtopics or concepts relevant to the subject under consideration. Place the citation of the relevant source (article/patent/website/data, etc.) in the corre"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the subject of the BRMK557?",
      "choices": [
        "engineering",
        "researcher",
        "research",
        "researchers"
      ],
      "answer_index": 0,
      "answer_text": "engineering",
      "explanation": "it is obvious that the number of papers relevant to a particular researcher is very few",
      "context_snippet": "RM& IPR– BRMK557. Syllabus Literature Review and Technical Reading, New and Existing Knowledge, Analysis and Synthesis of Prior Art, Bibliographic Databases: Web of Science, Google and Google Scholar, Effective Search: The Way Forward. A good literature survey is typically a two-step process as enumerated below. Identify the major topics or subtopics or concepts relevant to the subject under consideration. Place the citation of the relevant source (article/patent/website/data, etc.) in the corre"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is BRMK557 for?",
      "choices": [
        "research",
        "researcher",
        "literature",
        "researchers"
      ],
      "answer_index": 3,
      "answer_text": "researchers",
      "explanation": "It is obvious that the number of papers relevant to a particular researcher is very few",
      "context_snippet": "RM& IPR– BRMK557. Syllabus Literature Review and Technical Reading, New and Existing Knowledge, Analysis and Synthesis of Prior Art, Bibliographic Databases: Web of Science, Google and Google Scholar, Effective Search: The Way Forward. A good literature survey is typically a two-step process as enumerated below. Identify the major topics or subtopics or concepts relevant to the subject under consideration. Place the citation of the relevant source (article/patent/website/data, etc.) in the corre"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the most important part of a good literature survey?",
      "choices": [
        "citation",
        "bibliographic",
        "a paper",
        "researchers"
      ],
      "answer_index": 0,
      "answer_text": "citation",
      "explanation": "a two-step process as enumerated below",
      "context_snippet": "RM& IPR– BRMK557. Syllabus Literature Review and Technical Reading, New and Existing Knowledge, Analysis and Synthesis of Prior Art, Bibliographic Databases: Web of Science, Google and Google Scholar, Effective Search: The Way Forward. A good literature survey is typically a two-step process as enumerated below. Identify the major topics or subtopics or concepts relevant to the subject under consideration. Place the citation of the relevant source (article/patent/website/data, etc.) in the corre"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the term for a literature survey?",
      "choices": [
        "citation",
        "Bibliographic Databases",
        "academic databases",
        "bibliographic"
      ],
      "answer_index": 3,
      "answer_text": "bibliographic",
      "explanation": "a literature survey is typically a two-step process as enumerated below",
      "context_snippet": "RM& IPR– BRMK557. Syllabus Literature Review and Technical Reading, New and Existing Knowledge, Analysis and Synthesis of Prior Art, Bibliographic Databases: Web of Science, Google and Google Scholar, Effective Search: The Way Forward. A good literature survey is typically a two-step process as enumerated below. Identify the major topics or subtopics or concepts relevant to the subject under consideration. Place the citation of the relevant source (article/patent/website/data, etc.) in the corre"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the definition of a researcher?",
      "choices": [
        "researcher",
        "research",
        "researchers",
        "engineering"
      ],
      "answer_index": 0,
      "answer_text": "researcher",
      "explanation": "a good literature survey is typically a two-step process as enumerated below",
      "context_snippet": "RM& IPR– BRMK557. Syllabus Literature Review and Technical Reading, New and Existing Knowledge, Analysis and Synthesis of Prior Art, Bibliographic Databases: Web of Science, Google and Google Scholar, Effective Search: The Way Forward. A good literature survey is typically a two-step process as enumerated below. Identify the major topics or subtopics or concepts relevant to the subject under consideration. Place the citation of the relevant source (article/patent/website/data, etc.) in the corre"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does RM& IPR call a literature survey?",
      "choices": [
        "literature",
        "a paper",
        "researchers",
        "research"
      ],
      "answer_index": 0,
      "answer_text": "literature",
      "explanation": "a two-step process as enumerated below",
      "context_snippet": "RM& IPR– BRMK557. Syllabus Literature Review and Technical Reading, New and Existing Knowledge, Analysis and Synthesis of Prior Art, Bibliographic Databases: Web of Science, Google and Google Scholar, Effective Search: The Way Forward. A good literature survey is typically a two-step process as enumerated below. Identify the major topics or subtopics or concepts relevant to the subject under consideration. Place the citation of the relevant source (article/patent/website/data, etc.) in the corre"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does RM& IPR stand for?",
      "choices": [
        "research",
        "the web",
        "google",
        "resources"
      ],
      "answer_index": 3,
      "answer_text": "resources",
      "explanation": "RM& IPR– BRMK557",
      "context_snippet": "RM& IPR– BRMK557. Syllabus Literature Review and Technical Reading, New and Existing Knowledge, Analysis and Synthesis of Prior Art, Bibliographic Databases: Web of Science, Google and Google Scholar, Effective Search: The Way Forward. A good literature survey is typically a two-step process as enumerated below. Identify the major topics or subtopics or concepts relevant to the subject under consideration. Place the citation of the relevant source (article/patent/website/data, etc.) in the corre"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a great place to start one's search when one is starting out on a topic?",
      "choices": [
        "resources",
        "the web",
        "google",
        "research"
      ],
      "answer_index": 2,
      "answer_text": "google",
      "explanation": "Google is a great place to start one’s search when one is starting out on a topic",
      "context_snippet": "RM& IPR– BRMK557. Syllabus Literature Review and Technical Reading, New and Existing Knowledge, Analysis and Synthesis of Prior Art, Bibliographic Databases: Web of Science, Google and Google Scholar, Effective Search: The Way Forward. A good literature survey is typically a two-step process as enumerated below. Identify the major topics or subtopics or concepts relevant to the subject under consideration. Place the citation of the relevant source (article/patent/website/data, etc.) in the corre"
    }
  ]
